Jesse Ruiz

La Mirada, CA 90638 ◆ (714) 603-8254 ◆ Jesse_1749@Hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Strongly motivated individual with eight years of experience in audiovisual presentations, as well as a year in small networking experience, with a proven track record of leading small teams in technical environments to success, looking for a company that will allow me to further develop and use my technical skills. Currently waiting to take my Network+ exam.

SKILLS

Troubleshooting, Timeline Management, Technical Support and Client Services.

WORK HISTORY

Technical Lead, 05/2018 to Current

PSAV – Anaheim, CA

Set up, operate, and strike audio, lighting, and video equipment used in live events such as meetings, business conventions, and concerts. Lead teams on major sets/strikes, worked face to face with clients to ensure a good event. Configured house ethernet ports to proper VLANS and setup basic switches, etc.

Barista, 04/2017 to 07/2017

Night Owl – Fullerton, CA

Prepare or serve hot or cold beverages, such as coffee, espresso drinks, blended coffees, or teas.

Clean or sanitize work areas, utensils, or equipment.

Check temperatures of freezers, refrigerators, or heating equipment to ensure proper functioning.

AV/Media Lead, 08/2011 to 06/2017

FreedomHouse Church – Fullerton, CA

Responsible for the set-up, operation, and maintenance of the Audio equipment. Led the media team during set-up and during op's. Assisted with scheduling, researched and tested new equipment, trained anybody who joined the team.

Custodial Lead, 05/2015 to 04/2017

Walt Disney Company – Anaheim, CA

Maintain the cleanliness of Disneyland park, and act as guides to the guests. Lead duties included managing multiple small teams, keeping check on inventory, and handling work orders in a timely manner.

	- Education -	
High School Diploma: 06/2014 La Mirada High School - La Mirada, CA		
	CERTIFICATIONS	

PSAV Level 1 Networking PSAV Level 1 Video Switching PSAV Level 2 Audio Systems